

FREELANCE COPYWRITER · STUDENT

Columbus, OH, 43228

□ 234-263-8771 | ■j.vandyket@gmail.com | ★ www.jackvandyke.com | □ JackTVanDyke

"Never let the fear of striking out keep you from playing the game."

Summary

Creative and hard-working 22-year-old future web developer who is freelance copywriting while learning web development. I am eager to learn at all times and committed to working day in and day out to achieve my goals. I enjoy games, working out, and continuously learning. If you believe I'm a strong candidate for your organization in any role, I'd love to speak with you.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Linux
- · Attention To Detail
- · Time Management

Work Experience

Self-Employed Remote

Freelance Copywriter 2020 - Present

- Write advertising copy designed to effectively reach customers in the appropriate target markets to promote products and services.
- Discuss products and services with clients to learn all the details and specifications to ensure the appropriate advertising methods and themes
 are used.
- · Research what aspects will make products and services more appealing to customers to maximize the number of sales.

DoorDash Columbus, OH

Freelance Driver 2019 - Present

- · Loading, transporting, and delivering items to clients or businesses in a safe, timely manner
- Communicating with the restaurant and customer to ensure a successful delivery.
- · Reviewing orders before and after delivery to ensure that orders are complete, the charges are correct, and the customer is satisfied

FedEx Twinsburg, OH

PACKAGE HANDLER

2017 - 2019

- Responsible for physically loading and unloading packages by hand, including placing, pushing, lifting, carrying and pulling the item in an
 efficient and safe manner.
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Using safe package moving and handling techniques to help employees and minimize the risk of injuries.}$
- Communicating with fellow employees and supervisors.

Achievements & Awards_

2021 **Freelance Copywriter,** Sole Writer For Multi-Million Dollar Marketing Agency *Remote, U.S.A.*

2020 **Driver Rating**, Drove Throughout The Pandemic While Maintaining A 4.96 Driver Rating *Columbus*, *U.S.A*

2006 **Finalist**, Time's Person of the Year New York City, U.S.A

Education

WGU(Western Governors University)

Salt Lake City, Utah (Remote)

B.S. IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, ACCOUNTING

2019 - Present

• Classes rely on the ability to self-teach and manage your time.